<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Smile</title>
    <link>https://smileprettypls.github.io/Smile/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Smile</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://smileprettypls.github.io/Smile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Terms &amp; Conditions</title>
      <link>https://smileprettypls.github.io/Smile/terms-and-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smileprettypls.github.io/Smile/terms-and-conditions/</guid>
      <description>1. Definitions Unless inconsistent with the context, the expressions set forth below shall bear the following meanings: Client” means the party engaging with Smile on any matter, including, for purposes of receiving Services from Smile; “Data” means any data, including personal information as defined in the Protection of Personal Information, Act 4 of 2013 (“POPI”), the Electronic Communications, Act 25 of 2002 (“ECTA”) and any other applicable legislation in the jurisdiction where the Services are to be provided, supplied, stored, collected, collated, accessed, retained or processed by Smile on behalf of the Client, irrespective of the media or form; “Data Protection Legislation” means the laws relating to data protection in South Africa, including, but not limited to, the Electronic Communication and Transactions Act 25 of 2002 (ECTA), the Consumer Protection Act (CPA) 68 of 2008 and the Protection of Personal Information Act (POPI); “Deliverables” means any deliverable recorded in the SOW provided by Smile to the Client including any designs, software, programs, creative work, copy, documents, data or other materials developed by Smile expressly, specifically and exclusively at the request and instance of for the Client in terms of these Terms of Service; “Estimate” means a quotation, proposal or cost-estimate as more fully described below issued by Smile and accepted and signed by the Client in respect of Services to be provided and/or Deliverables to be delivered in terms of the SOW.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Big Up Yourself On Our Blog.</title>
      <link>https://smileprettypls.github.io/Smile/blog/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smileprettypls.github.io/Smile/blog/post-1/</guid>
      <description>Smile Smile is helping artists reach their goals. Learn about the free resources we have available for emerging artists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 tips for being a successful comedian</title>
      <link>https://smileprettypls.github.io/Smile/blog/post-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smileprettypls.github.io/Smile/blog/post-2/</guid>
      <description>1.Have Good Content Creating Good content is not easy becuase every single individual in your audience is different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://smileprettypls.github.io/Smile/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smileprettypls.github.io/Smile/about/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>contact</title>
      <link>https://smileprettypls.github.io/Smile/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://smileprettypls.github.io/Smile/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
